<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>http://cameronspickert.com/</id>
  <title>Cameron Spickert's Blog</title>
  <updated>2011-10-08T04:00:00Z</updated>
  <link rel="alternate" href="http://cameronspickert.com/"/>
  <link rel="self" href="http://cameronspickert.com/feed.xml"/>
  <author>
    <name>Cameron Spickert</name>
    <uri>http://cameronspickert.com</uri>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:cameronspickert.com,2011-10-08:/2011/10/08/implementing-oplop-in-python/</id>
    <title type="html">Implementing Oplop in Python</title>
    <published>2011-10-08T04:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2011-10-08T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://cameronspickert.com/2011/10/08/implementing-oplop-in-python/"/>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I've been using &lt;a href="http://oplop.appspot.com/"&gt;Oplop&lt;/a&gt; for a while now. It's a great alternative to database-style password management programs like &lt;a href="http://www.agilebits.com/onepassword"&gt;1Password&lt;/a&gt;, providing the same level of security without compromising portability. While 1Password lets you take your passwords with you via an encrypted file and mobile, web and desktop apps, Oplop makes it so you don't have to take anything with you at all!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I don't like about Oplop, however, is having to go to &lt;a href="http://oplop.appspot.com/"&gt;oplop.appspot.com&lt;/a&gt; every single time I need to retrieve my passwords. So I decided to implement &lt;a href="http://code.google.com/p/oplop/wiki/HowItWorks"&gt;the algorithm&lt;/a&gt; as a Python script with a simple command line interface.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script src="https://gist.github.com/1259200.js"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;


&lt;p&gt;From here, I just need to come up with a way to get passwords generated by the script into web forms and applications automatically. For now, &lt;a href="http://www.alfredapp.com/"&gt;Alfred&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;a href="http://www.alfredapp.com/powerpack/"&gt;+ Powerpack&lt;/a&gt;) and &lt;code&gt;pbcopy&lt;/code&gt; are doing nicely.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:cameronspickert.com,2011-08-30:/2011/08/30/uiimage-from-uiview/</id>
    <title type="html">Easily create a UIImage from a UIView</title>
    <published>2011-08-30T04:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-30T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://cameronspickert.com/2011/08/30/uiimage-from-uiview/"/>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;One of my projects at Aviary necessitated generating a static UIImage from a UIView. Fortunately, Quartz makes it really simple to do this. Here's a quick category on UIView showing how it can be done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To explain: -createImageFromRect: method generates an image by rendering the portion of the view bounded by "frame" in an image context. Note that CALayer's -renderInContext: method renders the entire layer tree, creating a flat image from the view hierarchy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;script src="https://gist.github.com/1181935.js?file=gistfile1.m"&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:cameronspickert.com,2011-08-28:/2011/08/28/aviary-hq/</id>
    <title type="html">Aviary HQ</title>
    <published>2011-08-28T04:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2011-08-28T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://cameronspickert.com/2011/08/28/aviary-hq/"/>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;A lot has happened in the past month or two, but the biggest news from me is that I started working at Aviary, Inc. in mid-July. I've been spending a good deal of time at the office, and I'm loving every minute of it. Our building is in the heart of Manhattan, right next to Penn Station and Madison Square Garden. We have an amazing roof and a really sketchy elevator. Hmm, reminds me of somewhere in Bushwick.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:cameronspickert.com,2011-07-08:/2011/07/08/reflecting-on-year-one-in-nyc/</id>
    <title type="html">Reflecting on Year One in NYC</title>
    <published>2011-07-08T04:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2011-07-08T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://cameronspickert.com/2011/07/08/reflecting-on-year-one-in-nyc/"/>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It's been an eventful year since I graduated last summer, made the transition from Cambridge to Bushwick. There's much more to this story, but I'm hoping this quick retrospective will kickstart this blog back into action.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Work&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A year ago was an exciting time for us: some friends and I had made &lt;a href="http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/rover-unofficial-guide-to/id312281600?mt=8"&gt;a successful iPhone app&lt;/a&gt; together, been &lt;a href="http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052748704188104575083293556739002.html"&gt;profiled by the Wall Street Journal&lt;/a&gt;, and received enough money from AT&amp;amp;T to work on mobile apps for schools AND live off of for a year. Times were good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We worked hard to get our work off the ground, finding our way with AT&amp;amp;T, some of their partner companies, and of course, universities, and ended up deploying the &lt;a href="http://itunes.apple.com/app/id441605750?mt=8"&gt;Columbia Business School mobile app&lt;/a&gt; last month after a year of hard work. While we didn't quite take our business to the level we wanted, we ended up with a product we can be proud of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As our team heads off in different directions, things are getting exciting once again. I'll have more to tell in a little over a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Life&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I'm convinced I'm a different person than I was when I arrived in New York City. It took a long time for me to get over how dirty, crowded and expensive it can be, but I'm learning to love it here--there really is no place like it. I've particularly enjoyed the &lt;a href="/2011/02/04/music-is-life-is-music/"&gt;live music scene&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bushwick has been great to me, and I'll miss it when I leave for Manhattan. I'm consistently amazed at how lucky we got with our apartment--even though our building has been an unexpected (or unwanted) adventure at times, we're around the corner from the L train, we now have a 24-hour grocery store across the street, and there are restaurants and shops popping up everywhere. We couldn't have asked for a better introduction to the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Happy New Year, NYC!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have lots of goals for the next year: getting a bike and commuting above-ground, getting more involved in the NYC startup scene, and meeting more people, to name a few. It's definitely going to be a busy year. Oh, and &lt;a href="/2011/02/04/music-is-life-is-music/"&gt;more concerts&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And, once again, I hope to make this blog worth reading!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:cameronspickert.com,2011-05-31:/2011/05/31/thompson-les/</id>
    <title type="html">Thompson LES</title>
    <published>2011-05-31T04:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2011-05-31T04:00:00Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" href="http://cameronspickert.com/2011/05/31/thompson-les/"/>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I went to a birthday party at a top-floor room at the Thompson LES (LES = "Lower East Side") on Sunday. As far as I can tell, it's the tallest building in the area, which made for an absolutely spectacular night-time view from the private deck. The room spans the length of the building and faces west, making for a perfect view of both the financial district, the Brooklyn Bridge, and midtown. I shudder to think what it would cost to actually stay here, and I'm glad the only cost to me was a bottle of rum.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>

